bosmaxhire.net 2016-01-25

# MaxHire :: Privacy Policy

## MaxHire Privacy Policy

MaxHire web sites collect and use your personal information to operate MaxHire Web sites and deliver the services you have requested. MaxHire sites also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from MaxHire and its affiliates. MaxHire may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

MaxHire does not disclose, sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. MaxHire may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. 

MaxHire keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within MaxHire in order to determine what MaxHire sites and services are the most popular. 

MaxHire Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on MaxHire or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of MaxHire. 

For questions about privacy, please email us at info@maxhire.net for more information. We welcome your feedback and support efforts to protect your privacy on the internet.
